My frlend Charlotte
was datlng Dr. Bram Walker...
...a very hardworklng orthopedlc surgeon.
Bram?
What?
Were you asIeep?
No, I was just resting my eyes.
My God.
I feII asIeep for one second.
I was up at 5:00, I had three carpaI tunneIs.
It's very exhaustive reconstructive work.
He feII asIeep when
he was making Iove to me.
He feII asIeep!
He was tired.
This has nothing to do with you.
Has a man ever faIIen asIeep
making Iove to you?
No, but I'm sure many of them wanted to.
I can't beIieve this happened to me!
You want some herb tea?
I must be reaIIy bad in bed.
You are not bad in bed.
I've got Constant Comment and....
Do you want some Tummy Tamer?
Of course it's her.
I have to say, I'm not surprised.
Ever seen her on a Stairmaster?
Nothing happening beIow the waist.
Nada. No saIe.
How can you say that?
Even if she was bad in bed,
which she isn't, is it reaIIy that important?
AbsoIuteIy. Who we are in bed
is who we are in Iife.
I never met a man who was bad in bed
who was good at Iife.
Just for the record, in bed, you are....
Don't make me state the obvious.
How can you be so sure?
No one ever took a nap whiIe fucking me...
...and I get affirmations aII the time.
Just Iast week....
Last week, Samantha had dlnner
wlth a gay couple she'd known for years.
Davld and Davld.
Thanks for a IoveIy dinner. It was fun.
I have to admit,
we have an uIterior motive.
What?
We're wondering if you're seeing
anyone speciaI right now?
ActuaIIy, no.
Do you have a hot guy for me?
Two.
-No!
-Yes!
We want to have sex with a woman.
-Are you serious?
-TotaIIy.
I'm curious about it.
We've never done it
and we thought it might be fun.
We were Iike:
''If we were gonna do it with a woman,
who wouId it be?''
-Then we were Iike, Samantha.
-TotaIIy.
We decided of aII the beautifuI women
we know, you are probabIy the best in bed.
TotaIIy.
Look at that!
I'm thinking about doing it.
They're cute, they're heaIthy.
They're gay!
For a sex coIumnist,
you have a Iimited view of sexuaIity.
Gay as pink suede.
Wake up. It's 2000.
The new miIIennium won't be about sexuaI
IabeIs, it'II be about sexuaI expression.
It won't matter if you're sIeeping
with men or women.
It'II be about sIeeping with individuaIs.
Or in your case, twos or threes.
Soon everyone wiII be pansexuaI.
It won't matter if you're gay or straight.
-Just if you're good or bad in bed.
-ExactIy.
That nlght I got to thlnklng about bed.
Are we secretly belng graded every tlme
we lnvlte someone to joln us ln lt?
A plus, B, D, lncomplete.
Is maklng love really nothlng
more than a pop qulz?
If sex ls a test, how do we know
lf we're passlng or falllng?
How do you know lf you're good ln bed?
Later on, I was walklng home thlnklng
about my sexual report card when....
What the heII--
Christ, I'm sorry. I didn't see you.
I threw my cigarette.
I thought I was stung by a bee. Jesus!
I'm sorry. Did it Ieave a mark?
You can't smoke in the restaurant.
I'm a smoker.
I'm a smoker too,
but watch where you throw those things?
No, it didn't Ieave a mark.
As the paln subslded,
my mlnd was free to notlce...
...how lncredlbly cute thls guy was.
I am sorry. My name's Patrick Casey.
Carrie Bradshaw, burn victim.
How weird was that? That was intense.
You gotta admit,
it's a cIever way to meet the Iadies.
You got a IittIe comedy routine
going there?
LittIe bit.
Listen, I reaIIy feeI bad.
At Ieast Iet me buy you a coffee,
or some burn saIve?
-Not funny yet.
-Sorry.
But it might be after a cappuccino.
There's a pIace right around the corner.
We can smoke there.
Three Marlboros and two
Marlboro Llghts later I had learned...
...Patrlck was a composer,
wrltlng muslc for movles.
What type of movies do you compose for?
ReaIIy bad ones.
The I Screamed When I Knew What You
Dld Last Summer On Elm Street types.
As Iong as you're chaIIenged
by what you do.
Dammit. Patrick Casey, whoever you are.
I'm Iate. I have to go.
Thank you for the coffee.
Maybe one day
you'II give me scar tissue again.
-You're great.
-Thanks.
As I walked away, I started to thlnk.:
How many cute, smart, slngle smokers
are there left ln the world? Seven?
I declded to do somethlng
I almost never do...
...glve a man my phone number.
This whoIe burn Iawsuit I pIan to initiate...
...it might get a IittIe crazy,
so here is my phone number.
You wiII need that for your attorney...
...or if you want to have
coffee again sometime.
I left feellng great. It was such a cute
approach. How could he not call?
How couId he not caII?
It's been three days.
Give him 12 more hours and then
send him off to the isIand of Iost men.
I don't wanna send him there, I Iike him.
CouId you beIieve that someone actuaIIy
had the nerve to caII this FIorentine Peach?
I can't beIieve you spent
this much on sheets.
It's an experiment.
I'm trying to change my bed karma.
I figure if I can make my bed
a pIace I reaIIy want to be...
...others wiII feeI the same way.
The fieId of dreams.
ExactIy. ''If you buiId it, he wiII come.''
The thing that gets me is, I'm not usuaIIy
wrong about the phone number size-up.
I don't put it out there
unIess I'm sure it's coming back.
I'm either reaIIy Ioving or hating the coIor.
He thinks I'm ugIy.
My God. Get a grip.
A guy doesn't caII you for three days
and you're ugIy?
-What's your point?
-PiIIowcase.
It's amazing.
We can feeI totaIIy good about ourseIves...
...and then it aII goes out the window
if the guy doesn't mirror it back to us.
This has a IittIe weird thing here.
Dammit. Does everything I bring into
this bedroom have to have a fIaw?
The next day I was ln the Vlllage looklng
for the perfect $7 dress...
...to go wlth my $300 shoes, when....
I had a cholce.
I could turn around and run away...
...or I could smlle, be brave
and walk on over.
Hi.
So what? Saturday's the day you stand on
the street and smoke in the ViIIage?
Hi, I'm Carrie.
-We're kind of in the middIe of something.
-Right, sure.
Bye. I was on my way to Perry Street.
This is Perry Street.
BIeecker, I meant BIeecker.
Okay, bye. Goodbye to you, too.
-Let me expIain.
-No, I'm embarrassed.
You're obviousIy in the middIe
of a thing with your Iover...
...or whoever and I'm there....
I'm not gay.
I'm an aIcohoIic.
We were waiting for a meeting to start.
I wanted to introduce you
but it's supposed to be anonymous.
I reaIIy wasn't getting the gay vibe
from you.
It's just, he was so cute and....
-I never caIIed.
-Right.
I was freaked. I've onIy been
in the program 11 months...
...and my sponsor said I reaIIy shouIdn't
get invoIved with someone for a year.
Okay, maybe you'II caII me in a month.
It doesn't bother you that I'm an aIcohoIic?
God, no. I Iove aIcohoIics.
HeII, I hope to be one someday.
-That was a joke.
-That's not funny, yet.
But it might be after a cappuccino.
What the fuck, it's onIy a coupIe of weeks.
WouId you Iike to go on a date sometime?
I can't think why not.
You caII me.
I accepted hls klnd lnvltatlon
because when you thlnk about lt...
...aren't we all ln recovery from somethlng?
Drlnklng? Drugglng?
Our last relatlonshlp?
On our flrst date,
Patrlck and I went for coffee.
I'm reaIIy compuIsive. If I open up a bag
of Chips Ahoy, I gotta eat the whoIe thing.
I'm Iike that with Reese's Pieces.
Reese's Pieces and shoes.
WouIdn't the shoes
be a IittIe tough on digestion?
This is me.
Thank you, Mr. Casey. I had a great time.
No, Miss Burn Victim.
I had the great time.
Then I gave hlm my very best
lean-ln-and-klss-me-goodnlght move.
Our next date, over dlnner,
he told me about worklng hls 12 steps.
After dlnner, I stood on my thlrd step
trylng to work hlm.
That smeII is amazing. What is that?
Me.
I'II caII you.
I couldn't flgure lt out.
I knew he wanted me, because durlng my
lean-ln-and-klss-me-goodnlght move...
...I'd accldentally, on purpose felt
hls pop-up-and-say-hello.
What was golng on?
By the thlrd date, I wanted hlm even more
than a flstful of Reese's Pleces.
WeII then, goodnight.
That was that. I'd hlt my humlllatlon llmlt.
Then I thought, how many cute,
smart, sexy, slngle, smoklng alcohollcs...
...are there left ln the world? Flve?
Do you want to come up?
But you see, the thing is,
I've never had sex sober.
I've aIways been drunk or high.
I don't know if I'II be any good.
What the heII?
Let's take it one step at a time.
Sex is amazing.
It feeIs so fucking amazing.
Do other peopIe know about this?
AII right! I did it! Sex without beer!
Easy, cowboy.
You!
What about you! You are the best.
You weren't haIf bad yourseIf.
You are the best.
-You're the best.
-I aim to pIease.
After we have a cigarette...
...can we do it again?
I'II have a Spanish omeIet, hash browns,
more coffee and orange juice.
Can I have some rice pudding
for Iater? Thanks.
Storing up for winter?
No, I'm starving. Patrick and I....
AII Iast night and I'm just....
No, don't stop, it's okay.
Just because I'm bad in bed
doesn't mean everybody is.
One more time.
You are not bad in bed.
ReaIIy? Has a man ever faIIen asIeep
making Iove to you?
No, but I once feII asIeep when a guy was
doing me. It was the Iudes.
It's okay.
I'm mature enough to reaIize that whiIe
I may be good at some things Iike...
...accessories, that I might need heIp
in others Iike....
-Fucking?
-Making Iove.
So, I'm taking a cIass.
A fucking cIass?
No, a tantric sex workshop.
Just don't drink any suspicious KooI-Aid
or put on new Nikes.
It's not Iike that. It's taught by a
weII-respected woman psychoIogist.
It's caIIed ''How To PIease A Man.''
I know how to pIease a man.
Just give away most of your power.
I have a trainer for the gym.
I can have a trainer for--
-Fucking?
-PIease stop saying that.
Are you actuaIIy going to do this?
Seating was Iimited,
so I signed you guys up.
PIease? I can't go aIone.
If Bram ever faIIs asIeep on me again,
I wiII die.
Pretty pIease, with sugar on it?
Christ, I'm in.
What the heII, I don't exactIy
have them hanging from the rafters.
''How To PIease A Man.''
I couId teach the damn cIass.
AII right.
That nlght,
whlle Davld and Davld got undressed...
...and walted for her ln the bedroom.
Samantha began to wonder
lf maybe she was about to go too far.
Was she actually capable
of belng thls sexually free?
Or was she gettlng ln over her head?
She declded before there were regrets,
they should all talk about lt a llttle more.
Listen, David and David, maybe....
You Iook amazing.
Just Iike Jean HarIow in Red Dust.
Samantha loved the Samantha mlrrored
through the eyes of the Davlds.
What the heII?
-They're so soft.
-I know.
-I can't do this.
-Neither can I.
But I....
-We're just getting start--
-No, can't.
-I'm sorry.
-Sorry.
It's very pretty, but no.
It's not you, it's us.
I have an idea. Let's aII put on our cIothes
and go out for geIati!
-Cheesecake.
-Whatever.
Suddenly, Samantha wasn't feellng
so good about herself ln bed.
I gotta go or I'm going to be Iate
for the tantric workshop thing.
Baby, you don't need a workshop.
You are amazing.
Come on, one more time.
We did it Iast night and aII this morning.
I couId have sex with you
morning, noon and night.
That's when I reallzed lt.
Mr. Compulslve wasn't ln bed wlth me...
More, c'mon.
...he was ln bed wlth a blg bag
of Chlps Ahoy.
More.
The intent of tantric...
...we say ''sacred sexuaIity...''
...is to experience
and merge with the Divine.
I think Patrick's addicted to me.
It's Iike he's repIaced drinking with me.
Program guys are tough.
I dated a guy who was
in Over-Eaters Anonymous.
Every time we had a fight,
he'd binge-eat hot fudge sundaes.
In other words, Iadies,
to drive your man crazy.
He wants to have sex aII the time.
It's getting a IittIe out of hand.
At Ieast he wants to fuck you.
-They were gay.
-So?
One minute they were interested and then,
suddenIy they weren't.
What did I do to turn them off?
Not having a dick wouId be the thing
that you did to turn them off.
You guys, I'm serious. This is rude.
Use it to bring any man to his knees.
With Iove, of course.
Where was this bitch Iast night
when I needed her?
Be quiet and you might Iearn something.
This Iady is supposed to be a genius.
If she's so good, why is she having
this workshop in her apartment?
I don't know.
Tantric sex is not about taIk,
it's about action.
DeIayed action.
So, without further deIay...
...Iet me introduce my husband.
Dr. Ronny Shapiro.
I wiII demonstrate the very effective...
...Lingham Massage.
I think I know why we're in an apartment.
The receiver Iies on his back...
...before the giver, naked.
GenitaIs cIearIy exposed for the massage.
You're not writing.
Take your time doing this.
An hour and a half later, crlppled by our
lnablllty to look away from a car crash...
...we watched as the Dr. Shaplro
lllustrated tantrlc sex.
Massage the head of the Lingham...
...as if you are using an orange juicer.
There go my good feeIings about breakfast.
Stop it! You're embarrassing me.
We're the embarrassing part?
PIace your right hand...
...on the receiver's Root chakra.
Root!
The Root chakra is Iocated between
the anus and the genitaIs.
I think that I just got my 50 bucks worth.
GentIy rock your hand
to awaken this chakra.
CIinicaIIy referred to as perineum.
Perineum: Latin for
''not without an engagement ring.''
WiII the women who are Iaughing
compose themseIves?
Thank you.
Orgasm is not the goaI
of Lingham Massage...
...but can be a pIeasant
and very weIcome side effect.
Watch what I'm doing here.
If you can master this...
...your man wiII aIways be faithfuI.
Because once they go tantric...
...they don't go back.
You go, girI.
See that? Can you aII see this?
My God!
He's gonna....
And just llke that,
Mlranda got hlt by Old Falthful.
What's funny?
After we talked Mlranda ln from
the ledge, I met Patrlck for a movle.
I was teIIing my sponsor today
how I feIt about you...
...and suddenIy I reaIized
maybe I shouId just teII you.
I Iove you.
There lt was, the llttle phrase
every glrl ls dylng to hear...
...a week and a half lnto a relatlonshlp.
Thanks and that's so....
What? Too soon?
Is that what you're thinking?
We have been going out for, Iike, a minute.
Fuck that shit. I don't want to pIay games.
I'm just trying to own my feeIings.
I Iove you. I said it.
Mr. Casey, you do not Iove me...
...you Iove you, not drinking, with me.
No, I Iove you.
I'm so fIattered...
...but I think maybe we shouId
sIow down a IittIe here.
What does that mean?
It means that things
are going very fast and....
You have these new feeIings
because you're not drinking--
No, don't give me that program buIIshit.
This has nothing to do with drinking.
I Iove you.
Maybe we shouId spend a IittIe time apart.
I'II caII you tomorrow.
-I'm not coming up?
-Just a coupIe of nights.
Are you breaking up with me? 'Cause if--
I'm not breaking up with you.
I'm just going inside.
CaII me tomorrow.
We'II do something next week, okay?
What am I going to do now?
You shouId go to a meeting.
And then go home, and caII me tomorrow.
Goodnight.
I'II see you next week.
Go.
Get yourseIf some cookies.
Meanwhlle, across town at Charlotte's....
My God, what are you doing?
My God.
You are good. Sweet Christ!
You are good!
Charlotte consldered lt the best 50 bucks
she'd ever spent.
It cost Mlranda a llttle more, but across
town ln her bed, thlngs were good as well.
CarrleI
What are you doing?
Fuck you, you bitch!
Shit!
I Ioved you and you didn't Iove me.
You fucking made me date you...
...before the month and now I'm drunk.
And I don't care!
I Iove you!
Make Iove to me!
What are you doing?
Don't take your cIothes off.
My flrst lmpulse was to go down
and rescue hlm...
...but as I learned on our second date,
that would be codependent.
Stlll, I felt I had to do somethlng.
Here, put this on, you'II get a coId.
I hope I fucking die!
Quiet, asshoIe, I'II caII the cops!
Shut the fuck up, dickweed!
Carrie!
You were the best fuck I ever had!
Three weeks later,
I got a letter from Patrlck...
...saylng he was back ln the program
and wanted to make amends.
I never saw hlm agaln
but I always wondered two thlngs.:
Was he able to stay sober?
Am I really that good ln bed?
欲望城市
（性爱专家凯莉布雷萧）
“是非对错”
夏绿蒂这阵子正在与
布莱姆沃克医生交往
他是个勤奋的整形外科医生
布莱姆？
-布莱姆？
-干嘛？
你睡著了吗？
-没有，我只是在闭目养神
-我的天
-好吧，我只睡了一秒钟
我从五点到现在都没睡
连续做了三个累人的重建手术
他和我做爱的时候竟然睡著了
他只是累了，这与你无关
男人和你做爱的时候
有睡著过吗？
没有，我想他们多半都想睡吧
-没想到这种事会落到我身上
-你要不要喝点药草茶？
-我在床上的表现一定很差劲
-你的表现不差劲
我这里有安抚情绪的
还是你想喝缓和腹部的茶？
当然是她的关系
这点我完全不惊讶
你看她做过踏板运动吗？
她的腰部以下都没有改变
就算她的技巧不高明
这很重要吗？
当然重要
床上的表现可以看出一个人
我没看过床上表现差劲的男人
在生活中有成就的
那你在床上的表现又如何？
-这需要我赘言吗？
-你怎么能这么肯定？
从来没有男人和我做爱睡著的
而且我每次都会得到证实
不过上星期…
上星期有一对同性恋
请莎曼珊吃饭
她认识他们好几年了
他们两个都叫大卫
谢谢你们邀我晚餐，我很愉快
-其实我们是别有用心
-甚么？
你现在有和谁在交往吗？
没有，你们要为我介绍谁吗？
有两个
-不会吧？
-你猜对了
我们想找个女人做爱
-你们是说真的吗？
-我一直很想体会那种感觉
我们都没和女人做过
那一定很有趣
我们想如果要找个女人
要找谁好呢？
我们就立刻想到了你
我们决定找个我们认识的
最漂亮的女人
-你的技巧一定也最出色
-没错
我答应他们考虑考虑
毕竟他们都是英俊的猛男
-他们是同性恋
-这是对性的一种狭隘的迷思
-男同性恋不是正常男人
-拜托，都已经两千年了
未来的一千年将是个
以性来表达的时代
这与你和男人或女人上床无关
-对方只是一个个体
-你现在是在搞三P
大家很快就会彼此交流
这和是不是同性恋无关
-重要的是你在床上的表现？
-没错
当晚我便在思考房事的问题
我们每次邀人共赴云雨时
是否都被打了分数？
诸如甲乙丙等或是不及格？
做爱和随堂测验
成了一回事吗？
如果性爱是一门测验
我们怎知是否及格了？
又怎么知道自己的表现如何？
那个星期我都在思考
我的性爱报告
搞甚么？那是甚么东西？
抱歉，我没看到你
我刚才在丢烟蒂
我还以为被蜜蜂螫了
抱歉，烫伤了吗？
餐厅里不能吸烟
我又是个老烟枪
我也是个老烟枪
但你丢东西应该小心点
我没有被烫伤
当疼痛消退之后
我才注意到这个人好帅
抱歉，我叫派崔克凯西
我叫凯莉布雷萧，烫伤患者
这种控诉太过强烈了
不过这样搭讪倒是挺高竿的
-原来这是你演的一出喜剧？
-有点那个意味
真的很抱歉
我请你喝杯咖啡作为补偿
不好笑
不过喝咖啡这提议不错
街角有家咖啡店
那里可以抽烟
在抽过两、三支烟之后
我发现派崔克在做电影配乐
你做的是哪种电影？
那都是些三流片
好比「去年夏天夜惊魂」
之类的电影
只要你对电影还有抱负就够了
糟糕，派崔克凯西
不管你叫甚么，我必须走了
谢谢你的咖啡
改天我再控诉内心受到的创伤
-你真会说话
-谢谢
当我离开的时候才想到
世上有几个长相与头脑兼具的
单身老烟枪？
七个吗？
接著我便做出破天荒的举动
给他我的手机号码
我这件烫伤诉讼
可能会有点难搞
这是我的电话号码
你请律师时会用到
或许下次可以再请我喝咖啡
这招让我自己都得意不已
他不打给我才有鬼
都过了三天他怎么还没打来？
再等他12小时
到时候就把他踢到荒岛去
我不想踢他走，我喜欢他
你相信有人把这种颜色
叫做佛罗伦斯桃红吗？
你怎么舍得在床单上
花这么多钱？
我在做一项试验
改变我的命运
我想如果能把床
布置成我的梦想乐园
别人也会感同身受
-你是说梦想乐土
-没错，所谓心想事成
没想到我给了电话的人
竟然不回我电话
我都是看准对象才给电话的
我现在对这个颜色
还没有明显的喜好
-他一定认为我很「爱国」
-拜托，别闹了
一个家伙三天不打电话给你
你就变成丑女了吗？
-你想说甚么？
-枕头套给我
我们原先都觉得自己很好
可是一走出去
男人要是不看我们…
这实在太荒谬了，该死
我费心打理的卧室
竟然还是有瑕疵
第二天我在街上找寻廉价洋装
好搭配我花三百美金买的鞋子
其实我这时候可以转身离去
但我却面带微笑
深呼吸一口气就走了过去
好好的星期六
你竟然站在大街上抽烟？
-你好，我叫凯莉
-我们正在谈事情
好的，我了解
-再见，我正要去佩里街
-这就是佩里街
我是说布利克街
再见，不打搅你们了
-凯莉，你听我解释
-不用，我是自找难堪
你显然正在和你的爱人谈事情
不，我不是同性恋
我只是有酗酒的毛病
我们正在这里等著聚会
我本来想为你介绍
但是我不能透露会友的名字
我并不是觉得你们像同性恋
只是他长得很帅，再加上…
-我没打电话给你
-没错
我戒酒已经11个月了
我的监护人要我在一年内
不能谈感情
好吧，那你一个月后再打给我
你不在意我是个酒鬼吗？
不会，我喜欢酒鬼
我甚至也想当个酒鬼
-我开玩笑的
-一点也不好笑
喝杯咖啡也许就不一样了
其实也不过只剩下几星期
你改天愿意出去吗？
有何不可？你再联络我
于是我便接受了他的邀约
其实每个人都在戒某些东西
好比戒酒、戒毒
甚至是戒上一段感情吗？
我们第一次约会是出去喝咖啡
我有点强迫症的毛病
只要打开一包洋芋片
就一定要整包吃完
蕊丝皮鞋一出新款
我也一定会去买
吃鞋子不太好消化吧？
我家到了
谢谢你，凯西先生
我玩得很愉快
烫伤小姐，我也过得很愉快
于是我示意他给我一个告别吻
第二次出去晚餐时他谈了
许多有关音乐的事
饭后我站在楼梯上企图勾引他
好香，这是甚么味道？
我
我再打电话给你
我实在想不通
我知道他想要我
因为在我靠近的时候
意外的感觉到他的小弟弟
正在对我「举枪致敬」
但他怎么没采取行动？
第三次约会时我对他的渴望
已经超过蕊丝皮鞋了
好了，晚安
我的羞辱已经到达了极限
但我又想到这个世上…
还剩几个聪明的帅哥？
五个吗？
-你想上去吗？
-想
但是我从来没在
清醒的时候做爱过
我总是喝得酪酊大醉
我不肯定自己的表现如何
管他的，船到桥头自然直
性爱真是太神奇了
真是不可思议
别人有这种感觉吗？
太棒了，我再也不怕做爱了
-冷静点，牛仔
-至于均KA
-你真是妙不可言
-你也不差
不，你是最棒的
我是很努力
等我们抽完这根烟…
可以再来一次吗？
我要一份蛋饼、马铃薯煎饼
再来一杯咖啡和柳橙汁
稍后再来一份布丁，谢谢
-你在准备冬眠吗？
-不，我快饿死了
我和派崔克忙了一夜
把我饿坏了
你尽管说，我的表现差
不表示你们都要和我一样
你在床上的表现一点也不差
有人在和你做爱的时候
睡著吗？
没有，但我有一次差点睡著
无所谓，我是个成年女人
我很清楚我对服饰搭配很在行
但某些事却需要别人帮助
-好比上床？
-做爱
所以我去报了一堂课
-学习床上技巧吗？
-不，是性爱研讨会
你只要别喝甚么诡异的饮料
或穿新布鞋就行了
讲师是一位
德高望重的心理学家
这堂课叫「如何愉悦男人？」
只要放弃你的权力
就能愉悦男人
我到健身房会找教练
当然也可以找人…
-教你做爱？
-别再说这个字了
你真的要去上课？
对，人数还有限制
我就帮你们报了名
拜托，我不能一个人去
布莱姆要是再在我身上睡著
我一定会死，拜托
-求求你们，好姊妹
-我去
好吧，其实去听听也无妨
如何愉悦男人？
我都可以开班授课了
好吧
当晚两个大卫先脱了衣服
在卧室里等她
莎曼珊才开始犹豫
这次玩得会不会太过火了
她能接受这种放荡的性爱吗？
还是她只是一时鬼迷心窍？
她认为在后悔之前
他们应该再商量一次
大卫，我想或许…
-你真的好美
-就像「红尘」里的珍哈露
莎曼珊立刻爱上了
他们眼中的自己
试试又有何妨
-真软
-没错
-我做不下去
-我也是
但是我…我们才刚开始
不，我做不下去，抱歉
抱歉，你的确秀色可餐
但我做不到
问题不在你，是在我们
不如这样吧？
我们穿上衣服去吃义大利果冻
-或是起司蛋糕
-都好
莎曼珊突然对自己丧失了信心
我得走了
不然会赶不上那个研习会
宝贝，你根本不用听那劳什子
你是个中高手，我们再来一次
昨晚和今早做得还不够吗？
和你整天整夜做爱我也不会腻
这时我了解到这个大男人
根本不是和我做爱
他是在和一大袋的洋芋片挣扎
「坦特罗」的意思就是
神圣的性爱
体验神人合一的感受
我看派崔克已经迷上我了
他想用我来取代酗酒
在戒酒的家伙都很难搞
我和一个暴食症患者交往过
我们只要一吵架
他就会开始狂吃圣代
换句话说
你能让你的另一半疯狂
他整天都想和我做爱
我都快控制不了了
-至少他还想碰你
-他们是同性恋
那又怎样？前一秒还兴致高昂
下一秒就没了兴致
我到底做错了甚么？
错就错在你没有老二
姊妹们，这太没礼貌了
你可以用爱让任何一个男人
对你俯首称臣
我昨晚需要她的时候
这个女人在哪里？
安静听你们就会学到东西
她是这方面的天才
她如果真的这么行
-干嘛在公寓里开这个研习会
-不要问我
「坦氏性爱」不重理论
而重于行动
我们也要为大家示范
现在就立刻开始
容我介绍我的先生
罗尼莎菲洛博士
由我来示范…
最有效的生殖器按摩术
我终于明白为甚么在这开课了
接受按摩者必须赤裸的
躺在按摩者前方
让生殖器完全曝露出来
你根本没在做笔记
按摩需要耐心
如果是车祸一个半小时后
或许还看不到车祸的真相
但这对夫妇却呈现了
坦氏性爱的效果
把你的手当成果汁机一样
按摩龟头部分
我早上吃的东西快吐出来了
别吵了，别丢我的脸好吗？
现在丢脸的是我们吗？
接著抬起右手
握住对方的命根子
命根子
它就位在肛门和外生殖器之间
看来这五十元美金很值得
轻轻的唤醒这个部分
这个部位在医学上叫做会阴
在拉丁语的意思就是
「结婚一定要有婚戒」
请那位在笑的小姐安静，谢谢
高潮虽然不是这种按摩的目的
却是种非常愉悦的副作用
请各位注意
只要掌握住诀窍
保证男人会永远效忠于你
因为他们只要做过这种按摩
就永远忘不了
加油
看到没？看清楚了没有？
我的天，他快要…
米兰达还被他的精液喷到了
有这么好笑吗？
那天稍晚我和派崔克去看电影
我今天和监护人谈起
我对你的感觉
我觉得我应该告诉你
凯莉
-我爱你
-老实说
这是每个女人在交往之后
都想听到的一句话
谢谢你，我真的觉得…
你觉得进展得太快了吗？
我们只交往了几天而已
可是我不想玩游戏
我只想忠于自己的感觉
我爱你
凯西先生，你并不是爱我
而是爱上清醒的感觉罢了
不，我爱你
你听我说…
我真的受宠若惊
我们或许该放慢一点
-甚么意思？
-事情发展得太快了
你初次体验到不喝酒的感觉
不，别对我说这些聚会的说辞
这件事和喝酒无关
我爱你
或许我们该分开几天
-我明天打电话给你
-我不能上楼去吗？
-忍耐几晚就好了
-你要和我分手吗？
派崔克，我不是要和你分手
我只是要进屋去
你明天打电话给我
我们下星期再碰面好吗？
-那我现在怎么办？
-你应该去聚会了
然后回家，明天打电话给我
晚安，下星期见
走吧
买点饼乾来吃
这时候夏绿蒂正在家里…
夏绿蒂，你在做甚么？
夏绿蒂，你真棒
我的天，你真棒
夏绿蒂认为那是她花过
最值得的五十元美金
米兰达花的钱虽然比较多
但结果也不错
凯莉
派崔克，你在做甚么？
-你这个臭婆娘
-该死
我爱你，你却不爱我
你让我在完成戒酒前一个月
就和你约会
现在我又开始酗酒了
我不在乎
凯莉，我爱你
我爱你，和我做爱
你在做甚么？别把衣服脱掉
我第一个念头是冲下去救他
但我在和他第二次出去时知道
这会变成一种惯性
但我还是想做点甚么
把这穿上，你会著凉的
我真希望我死掉
-你再不安静我就报警
-你给我闭嘴
凯莉，你是我上过最棒的女人
三星期后派崔克写了封信给我
说他又回去戒酒了
之后我没有再见过他
但我一直在想两件事情
一是他戒酒有没有成功？
还有我在床上真的这么棒吗？